<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[165]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Britain starts talks with UAE for post-Brexit trade deal]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[UK International Trade Secretary Liam Fox took part in 'high-level political and business discussions with UAE officials and businesses' during the World Government Summit in Dubai.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-04-09]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[167]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[KES forum discusses challenges, opportunities of tech projects]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait’s $200m Tech Fund a step towards embracing digital technology: Expert. KUWAIT: Kuwait Economic Society (KES) hosted a forum titled ‘Tech Projects in Kuwait: Challenges and Opportunities’, geared towards startups.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-04-09]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[169]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[NRIs make a wish list ahead of Indian budget]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Most pin little hopes on spending plan ahead of general elections this year]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-04-09]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[500]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Why cryptocurrencies are facing an uncertain future]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[However, strong volumes and large transaction figures point towards potential push upwards by end-2019.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-06-23]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[502]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[The Winners and the Losers in the Trade War Between US and China]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Analysts expect that the US dollar, Japanese yen and Swiss franc will be major beneficiaries.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-06-05]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[504]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[US-China trade war: The winners and losers]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Investors have to carefully pick assets, from currencies to commodities.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-06-04]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[506]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Marmore: GCC Sovereign Wealth Funds Dominate in Asset Growth]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[With the aim of reducing their dependency on hydrocarbons, diversification efforts of the GCC states have surged...]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-07-05]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[510]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Markaz: Oil Rally Fuels Stock Markets in GCC]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia and Kuwait stand out for the year.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-05-04]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[511]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[For rebounding Dubai IPO market, liquidity remains key]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The Initial Public Offering (IPO) market in Dubai is likely to see a rebound this year after a long period of lull.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-04-27]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[513]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Performance of most GCC markets improve: Markaz]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait and Saudi Arabia clock 12% yearly gain each in 2019.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-04-08]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[514]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[SME sector in GCC Region]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Small and Medium-sized Enterprises (SMEs) across the world play a dynamic role in industrialization.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-04-02]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[516]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Marmore-Markaz: Consultants bring high influence on policies but variable on implementation in the GCC economies]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Marmore-Markaz: Consultants bring high influence on policies but variable on implementation in the GCC economies.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-03-31]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[517]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GISS, MPHC stocks surge on Energy Bank announcement]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[After past couple of weeks’ muted performance, Qatar stocks rebounded yesterday as investors took refuge in blue chips.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-03-28]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[520]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Banks will drive GCC earnings growth for 2019]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Amidst muted growth expectations in the global markets, economic outlook for GCC region as a whole remains positive.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-03-26]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[522]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Knowledge partnership aiming to provide innovative research in the GCC]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Marmore MENA Intelligence signs MoU with TAC ECONOMICS.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-03-19]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[523]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[M&A sweeping across GCC banking sector calls for in-depth research to maximize benefits: Raghu]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[During Markaz's seminar organized in collaboration with Kuwait Banking Association.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-03-11]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[524]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Emaar, Emirates NBD top list of GCC 'bargain stocks']]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Two of Emaar's listed companies, several of the Gulf's top banks, ranked highly on the Markaz list of undervalued stocks.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-03-10]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[924]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Investcorp's Co-CEO Rishi Kapoor Is Courting Growth By Looking East]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The Bahrain-based firm had acquired IDFC, a private equity business in India]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-07-04]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[926]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[India budget to focus on rural economy, jobs]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Analysts and experts said the government is expected to cut taxes on business]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-07-04]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[1072]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Party Mood Sours in Saudi Markets After $20 Billion Bonanza]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Expected inflows from inclusion in EM indexes set to taper. Wooing active managers likely ‘a hard grind’...]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-07-14]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[1481]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Government initiatives, low valuations to trigger UAE markets rebound: Daman Investments]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Dubai-based Daman Investments is optimistic about UAE stock markets...]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-08-05]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[1708]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Markaz: GCC markets feel the impact of trade war]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Markaz report stated that GCC markets ended the month of August in negative territory.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-09-01]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[1710]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Higher foreign ownership limits to boost UAE investment flows]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Increasing foreign ownership would enable UAE banks to broaden investor base.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-09-08]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[1759]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Boursa Kuwait set for boost from index upgrade and oil sell-offs]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Boursa Kuwait’s 176 listed companies, nearly three-quarters of their weight.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-09-10]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[1924]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[MENA Funds: Best and worst performers in H1 2019]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Which funds were the main gainers and losers for H1 2019 and the last five years in the UAE, Saudi Arabia and Egypt?]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-09-17]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2078]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[AUM Industry Poised For Growth]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The asset under management (AUM) industry in Qatar is still in a nascent stage but is poised to grow in the coming years as the government is encouraging more investors including foreigners to derive maximum benefit from this untapped industry with large potential.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-09-25]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2294]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Markaz: Geopolitics influence GCC Markets in September, Oil turns volatile]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait's All Share Index fell for the second straight month, down by 4.4% during September, suffering from the profit booking after the MSCI EM index inclusion announcement in July]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-10-02]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2295]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[India vows to revive growth as RBI cuts rates again]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Central bank in fifth straight cut this year, will stick to accommodative stance as needed]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-10-04]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2296]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Expo 2020: Dubai likely to see 4% growth in the next 12 months]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Emirate expected to grow over 4% in next one year as economic activity gains momentum]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-10-19]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2348]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[CNBC Arabia Interview with M.R Raghu about Kuwait Fintech]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait Fintech Conference]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-10-28]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2358]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Fintech Talk - Future of Financial Services]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[M.R. Raghu, CFA, FRM, FCMA, EVP, Published Research, Markaz and MD of Marmore, speaking at ‘FinTech’ talk organized by KFAS]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-10-30]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2375]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[How visa reforms boost UAE economy]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The UAE government has opened up visas to welcome foreign investments and boost trade ties as it serves the Mena region as the gateway for the same.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-11-03]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2409]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Aramco world’s most profitable company in 2018]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Oil giant Saudi Aramco revealed yesterday it made the world’s biggest corporate profit last year, opening its secretive accounts for the first time as it prepares to raise funds from investors. ]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-04-01]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2435]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Liquidity measure: Liquid assets to total assets ratio of GCC Islamic banks]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The liquidity conundrum is one that has been discussed at great length especially in the Islamic banking context, where there is a dearth of instruments to effectively manage liquidity.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-11-13]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3101]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait ended the year as the best performing GCC market in 2019: Markaz]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The strong rally in Kuwait equities during the year stemmed from MSCI’s decision to include Kuwait in its emerging market indices from next year.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-01-07]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3104]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE's non-oil private sector posts slowest growth in 8 years in December]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Conditions in the UAE’s non-oil private sector have remained subdued, as businesses struggle to keep sales up and stimulate demand amid stiff competition, according to new data.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-01-06]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3127]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Reasons why Saudi Arabia is the most attractive MENA market for retail investments]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia is the most attractive developing market for retail investment in the Middle East and North Africa (Mena) and among the top ten in the world, according to the 2019 Global Retail Development Index (GRDI) from global management consultancy firm A.T. Kearney. ]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-12-16]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3128]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE banks prove resilience again with bumper profits]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[UAE banks posted strong profits in the first half of 2019 and this trend is expected to continue in the second, with local and international dynamics dictating the country's banking sector.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-08-11]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3129]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait’s MSCI upgrade to attract $3-6bln of passive inflows: analyst]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[MSCI announced on Tuesday that it would upgrade Kuwaiti equities to emerging markets status in its May 2020 semi-annual review]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-06-26]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3130]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Markaz launches a special publication titled Souq Al-Manakh and five other GCC crises]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The publication covers major financial crises such as Souq Al-Manakh, the subprime crisis in 2008, Dubai 2009 Real Estate Meltdown, the default of a major Saudi group]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-06-23]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3131]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Daman Investments to launch two new funds]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Dubai-based Daman Investments is launching two new funds, with the first targeting conventional investors and the second being offered to those seeking shariah-compliant investments, the company’s head of asset management has told Zawya.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-03-26]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3132]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[M&A among strategies in GCC banking sector to enlarge benefits]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Mergers and acquisitions (M&A) are one of the widely adopted corporate strategies that endorse the growth of an organization; however, not all mergers yield positive outcomes, according to Raghu, executive vice president (EVP) and head of research at Markaz and managing director of Marmore MENA Intelligence, a research subsidiary of Markaz.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-03-11]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3133]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[More in the tank: Higher oil prices dent Gulf bond and sukuk issuance in 2018 - report]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[A higher average oil price over the course of 2018 meant Gulf governments tapped debt capital markets less frequently throughout the year, a new report has said.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-01-13]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3134]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE investors get money’s worth by betting big on dividend stocks]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Regional investors who were unsure if they should put their hard-earned money in stocks and sought shelter in high dividend-paying companies rightly reaped heaps in dividend payouts this year.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-12-31]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3135]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Saudi Aramco shares extend losing streak to third day]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Saudi Aramco shares extended a losing streak to a third day on Thursday, shedding much of their initial gains seen after a blockbuster initial public offering as investors take profits.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-12-19]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3138]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Investors hope Qatar dairy will be cash cow]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The cows of Qatar’s Baladna farm, housed in climate-controlled farms in the desert, exemplify the lengths to which Qatar has gone to resist what it calls an economic “blockade” enforced by its Saudi-led neighbors.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-11-06]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3140]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Milking it: investors hope Qatar's desert dairy will be cash cow]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The cows of Qatar's Baladna farm, housed in climate-controlled farms in the desert, exemplify the lengths to which Qatar has gone to resist what it calls an economic "blockade" enforced by its Saudi-led neighbours.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-11-06]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3141]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Markets to stay bearish ahead of Aramco IPO]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The regional bourses will stay bearish in the coming weeks, ahead of Aramco's IPO as retail investors will sell their holdings to raise cash to subscribe the Saudi giant's share offering, say analysts.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-11-05]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3143]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Dubai seeks investments to bolster its economy]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[With the highest tower in the world, grand commercial centres and artificial islands, Dubai projects an image of prosperity, even as the city-state races to court investors to bolster it economy.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-10-05]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3145]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Dubai seeks investment to bolster flagging economy]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[With the highest tower in the world, grand commercial centres and artificial islands, Dubai projects an image of prosperity, even as the city-state races to court investors to bolster a flagging economy.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-10-04]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3146]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Oil producers to weigh output cuts at this week’s meet]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Top oil producers will consider fresh output cuts at a meeting this week, but analysts are doubtful they will succeed in bolstering crude prices dented by the US-China trade war.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-09-08]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3147]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Analysts hail RBI's repo cut to 6.25%]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of India's decision to cut the repo rate to 6.25 per cent will benefit the Non-resident Indians (NRIs) who intend to take a loan, or are already having a loan based on floating interest rates, experts have said.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2019-02-07]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3182]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Markaz: GCC market outlook 2020 mostly Stable despite volatility]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait Financial Centre 'Markaz' recently released its outlook on GCC markets for the full year of 2020.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-01-19]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3184]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Outlook mostly stable despite volatility]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Markaz analyses the performance of GCC stock markets in 2019 and provides an outlook for 2020 based on  a four-force framework that includes economic outlook, corporate earnings potential, valuation  attraction, and market liquidity, for all the GCC markets. ]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-01-19]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3607]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC equities and coronavirus: Minimal impact in the UAE, Saudi stocks suffer losses]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Oil prices dropped 11.9% on concerns over oil demand from China]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-02-03]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3799]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[US dollar turns safe haven for investors]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The yen fell past 112 to a 10-month low against a broadly stronger US dollar on Thursday, extending recent losses for the Japanese currency as investors fretted about dire economic news out of the country.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-02-23]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3895]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Panic Selling Hits Stocks]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The sharp reactions to bearish cues were evident as global indices unleashed fear and panic and investors resorted to heavy selling on Friday over the Covid-19 spread.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-02-29]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3936]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait markets pulled down by Coronavirus hurdle]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[S&P GCC composite index declines by 7.4% ]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-03-04]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3972]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[More than $200bn wiped off Gulf markets in huge one-day slump]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Hundreds of billions of dollars were wiped off Gulf markets on Sunday after they were hit with their biggest one-day fall sell-off in 15 years. More than $180bn was wiped off from the region's biggest bourse, Saudi Arabia's Tadawul, while trading in the Kuwait Premier Market index was suspended for the second time in six days after hitting a daily decline limit of 10 per cent in company share values.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-03-09]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3973]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[India stocks, rupee plunge on global cues]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The Indian stock markets plunged today wiping out Rs6.5 trillion equity investors' wealth, with Sensex recording a loss of 2,400 points and Nifty50 trading below 10,400 points. The domestic indices were in line with the global markets on persistent fears of economic impact of the coronavirus epidemic.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-03-09]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4155]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC IPOs could be delayed as coronavirus outbreak hurts investor appetite]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[As many as 16 IPOs expected to take place in 2020 may not materialize]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-03-23]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4172]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Global recession now inevitable as coronavirus continues to spread: analysts]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Some economies in Europe, Asia will be worst hit, add analysts]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-03-12]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4173]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Coronavirus to hurt GCC's real estate, hospitality, banking sectors - S&P]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Ratings agency says crisis will also reduce region's export volumes]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-03-12]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4174]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE stocks bounce back after US-Iran turbulence]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Benchmarks on DFM, ADX wipe out steep losses recorded at peak of Middle East crisis]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-01-13]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4410]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Middle East faces a long, ‘ugly’ recession amid coronavirus fallout: Experts]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The IMF predicted last week that coronavirus would likely cause the greatest global recession in nearly a century...]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-04-20]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4425]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Middle East faces a long, ‘ugly’ recession: Experts]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The Middle East is facing a long and “ugly” recession as the coronavirus pandemic stifles economic activity, experts said.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-04-20]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4426]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Coronavirus: Emerging markets, including Saudi Arabia, headed for recession?]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Emerging Markets economies facing severe stress resulting from health crisis: S&P]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-04-01]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4428]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[India budget fails to deliver on stimulus]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Too much of capital outlay on agriculture comes at the expense of cash starved industry]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-02-02]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4430]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait’s fiscal buffers bring breathing space]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Economic optimism across the six countries of the Gulf Co-operation Council (GCC) is in short supply going into the second quarter of 2020. ]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-04-01]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4433]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Reforms put Kuwaiti stocks on investors' radars]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The evolution of Kuwait’s capital markets has illustrated the country’s economic transformation of the past 10 years.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-04-01]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4434]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Gulf stock markets hit as coronavirus sinks crude oil prices]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Demand in China, world’s biggest oil importer, has slumped 20 percent as coronavirus takes its toll]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-03-02]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4436]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Gulf Bourses Down as Coronavirus Spreads]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Stock markets in the Gulf slumped on Sunday on fears the spreading coronavirus outbreak could hurt the global economy and oil prices.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-03-01]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4438]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Expo 2020 Dubai Organizers Recommend One-Year Postponement]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Organizers of Expo 2020, a multi-billion-dollar world trade fair originally scheduled to open in Dubai in October, on Monday recommended a one-year postponement due to the coronavirus pandemic.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-03-30]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4440]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Coronavirus compounds Gulf economic woes as oil prices slump]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Capital Economics estimates the 6 Gulf Cooperation Council states will lose some $40 billion of oil revenues in 2020]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-03-05]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4442]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Coronavirus Effect: Gulf Countries Face Economic Woes as Oil Prices Slump]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The Gulf region is already struggling to cope with decreasing oil revenues as the public health crisis paralyses economic giant China, the world's biggest oil importer and buyer of Gulf oil.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-03-04]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4612]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Is this the right time to invest in property? Experts weigh in]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Although distress sales and deals abound in the market, beware of price volatility and falling yields]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-05-20]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4888]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[COVID-19 hits Middle East construction activity]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[M.R Raghu, said that although the GCC construction market continued to remain buoyant, with projects worth $17.5bn announced in February 2020 alone, the supply of materials was bound to face constraints.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-06-01]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5391]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait Stocks Drop With Emir in Hospital, S&P Outlook: Inside EM]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait’s main equity index led losses in the Gulf after the country’s ruler was hospitalized over the weekend and S&P Global Ratings downgraded the prospects for the economy.

]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-07-19]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5423]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty drop as investors eye Fed meeting today]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The Indian stock markets witnessed choppy trend as they traded in negative in mid-day trading.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-07-29]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5578]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Are there investment lessons to be learned from epidemics/pandemics?]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The coronavirus-induced market correction is only temporary, reassure wealth managers]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-06-24]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5594]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Covid-19 crisis: UAE, GCC firms’ Q2 net profits set to plunge]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[UAE and GCC companies will report a significant drop in their second-quarter earnings due to higher provisions and lower revenues in the wake of the Covid-19 crisis, according to experts.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-07-21]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5596]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC's Borrowing Binge]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[GCC-based countries are drawing down their foreign exchange reserves to protect their dollar pegs and tapping global debt markets for record amounts, along with corporates.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-07-28]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5598]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Beirut blast: Lebanon's economy, currency likely to weaken further]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The Lebanese pound has already lost more than 80 per cent of its value since October last year.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-08-05]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5830]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait ousts blue-collar expats as slump, resentment bite]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The cash-strapped govt said last month that from January it will no longer renew work permits for expatriates over the age of 60 without university degrees]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-09-10]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5834]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait ousts blue-collar expats as slump, resentment bite]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Like its Gulf neighbours, Kuwait depends heavily on cheap foreign labour, mainly Middle Eastern and Asian workers.

]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-09-10]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6225]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait: A compelling proposition (Cover Story)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[MR Raghu pointed out that Islamic banks still entered the current pandemic in a very good position in terms of asset quality, profitability and capitalization…]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-10-28]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6227]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Vote of confidence for volatility]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Some economists predict that Democrats and Republicans are unlikely to agree on a stimulus deal before the November 3 elections.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-10-25]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6229]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE lenders banking on gradual recovery]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Financial institutions' performance to largely depend on economic rebound]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-08-15]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6297]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE's legal reforms to boost its status as expat, investment destination]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Move can incentivise 'greater business participation' ]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-11-10]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6299]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait Stocks’ Big Moment Lacks the Usual Pre-Upgrade Rally]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwaiti companies will enter the popular emerging-market stocks benchmark compiled by MSCI Inc. this month.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-11-09]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6301]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait stocks’ big moment lacks usual pre-upgrade rally]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[MSCI is due to unveil its semi-annual index review on Tuesday, disclosing Kuwaiti shares to be added to the MSCI Emerging Markets Index..]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-11-09]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6303]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Qatar- Kuwait stocks' big moment lacks usual pre-upgrade rally]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwaiti companies will enter the popular emerging-market stocks benchmark compiled by MSCI Inc this month.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-11-09]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6314]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Oil-rich Kuwait faces reckoning as debt crisis looms]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[COVID, low oil prices and the liquidity crisis have all come together in a perfect storm

]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2020-11-24]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6528]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Markaz House Views 2021: Opportunities and Outlook]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Join Markaz webinar titled ‘Markaz House Views 2021: Opportunities and Outlook’ to hear Markaz investment professionals share their expert opinion on current market conditions and provide outlook for 2021.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2021-01-18]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6644]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Budget sops boost Indian stocks]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The Indian stock markets welcomed the much anticipated budget 2021-22 by Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman on Monday, showing bullish cues.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2021-02-01]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6699]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Saudi plan to lure multinationals will boost job creation and knowledge transfers]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Move will fast-track the country's goal to make Riyadh one of the top 10 city-economies in the world]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2021-02-16]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6700]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Markets cheer as Sensex crosses 2,000 points, Nifty up by 500 points]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The Indian stock markets cheered on Monday in the mid-trading session as stocks cross 2,000 points]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2021-02-01]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6855]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Operation Suez success as monster ship refloated]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Intense salvage efforts lasting 7 days free mega ship and 367 ships affected by the blockage]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2021-03-30]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6856]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Megaship blocks Suez Canal for third day: Why it matters to oil prices, world trade]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Billions worth of commodities, crude and goods pass through it... If the blockade is cleared within a day, the implications could be minimal. However, if the situation persists for five days or more, the ramifications could be massive]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2021-03-25]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[7212]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Dubai Shares Lead Mideast Gains on Property Optimism: Inside EM]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The major contributor to the recent rally in Kuwait Premier Markets has been the surge in Agility’s shares]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2021-05-09]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9000]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE’s weekend change to boost economic competitiveness]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The step will also lead to better integration of the local economy with global financial markets, analysts say]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2021-12-08]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9156]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[What is the Dubai talent pass, how much does it cost and who can apply?]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Dubai Airport Free Zone launched the pass to attract freelancers in the media, art, culture, technology and education sectors]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-01-12]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9158]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE Proposed Corporate Tax: Mr. Raghu Interview]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Companies in the UAE are gearing up for the new tax on profits- the first of its kind in the country- coming into effect in June 2023.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-02-02]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9160]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Will a new tax dent business-friendly Dubai?]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Interview of our CEO M.R. Raghu, CFA, FRM, FCMA. with CNN Business on UAE tax]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-02-03]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9257]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Mentor For India @ 100]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Mr. M.R. Raghu, CFA, FRM, FCMA CEO of Marmore MENA Intelligence is #Mentor for INDIA@100. ⁠]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-02-23]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9259]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Markaz to share insights on evolving market dynamics during Doha Bank's webinar]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Contributing to enhancing the local and regional business environment and positive investor sentiment in the post-pandemic landscape]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-02-22]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9284]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Europe is the most affected by the imposition of sanctions on the Russian energy sector]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Interview of our CEO M.R. Raghu, CFA, FRM, FCMA. with Bloomberg ashraq.com on Imposing sanctions on the Russian energy sector.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-03-08]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9286]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Russia's Central Bank action]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Interview of our CEO M.R. Raghu, CFA, FRM, FCMA. with Bloomberg ashraq.com on Russia's Central Bank action]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-02-28]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9301]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait inflation hits decade high as food prices soar by 7.2%]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Markaz subsidiary Marmore says Kuwait’s inflation is now one of the highest rates among GCC countries]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-03-15]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9366]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[What the UAE's decision on listing co-ops will mean for the market]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The country is taking several measures to boost its financial markets and attract new investors]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-03-22]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9368]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Dollar prices have not reached the peak yet]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Interview of our CEO M.R. Raghu, CFA, FRM, FCMA. with Bloomberg ashraq.com on the dollar prices have not reached a peak yet.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-03-23]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9370]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Global Economy]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Interview of our CEO M.R. Raghu, CFA, FRM, FCMA. with Bloomberg ashraq.com on Global Economy]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-03-30]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9389]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[How the impact of western sanctions on Russia could affect GCC states]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Marmore MENA Intelligence says macro-economic impact of sanctions on Russia by the west can be substantial and bilateral relations between Russia and the GCC are important]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-04-18]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9425]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Revealed: The countries leading the FDI surge into Dubai]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The UAE continues to launch incentives to attract foreign investment and overseas talent]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-05-11]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9439]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[The UAE economy's transformation under Sheikh Khalifa's leadership]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed, who died on Friday at the age of 73, presided over the UAE’s transformation into a progressive economy.
]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-05-14]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9444]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Sheikh Khalifa, ‘master statesman’ who put UAE on the map]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Analysts pay tribute to the visionary leader who transformed his region]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-05-16]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9505]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE’s aluminium drive is out of this world]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Aluminium has been a bedrock of the UAE’s economy and its industrial ambitions for years with exports reaching more than 50 countries around the world.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-05-24]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9522]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[High inflation and slowing growth could lead to recession]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Interview of our CEO M.R. Raghu, CFA, FRM, FCMA. with Bloomberg ashraq.com - High inflation and slowing growth could lead to recession
]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-05-30]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9552]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Canada and Dubai grow closer with every deal struck]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[A Canadian pension fund company’s decision to invest $5 billion in UAE multinational logistics company DP World’s assets is a striking example of the deepening commercial ties between the two countries.  ]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-06-07]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9591]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[The Fed will keep raising interest rates until the end of 2023]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Interview of our CEO M.R. Raghu, CFA, FRM, FCMA. with Bloomberg ashraq.com - The Fed will keep raising interest rates until the end of 2023]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-06-18]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9618]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[From chocolate to solar power, the UK-GCC trade deal is a winner]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[A comprehensive free trade agreement between the six GCC nations and the UK would be a milestone]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-06-23]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9636]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Dubai takes roadshow to Africa, India and Europe to court startups]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Accelerator programmes and incubators help startups at different stages of the business cycle, by providing them with advisory, networking and administrative support services.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-06-27]]></date>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[9641]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UK’s offer of visa-free travel to UAE hailed as ‘historic’ step]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[UAE has been a key market to the UK in terms of inbound tourism, featuring among the top 10 countries by inbound visitor spending in 2019.]]></content>
		<date><![CDATA[2022-06-28]]></date>
	</node>
</data>
