<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[152]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Value Traded (In USD Mn)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[A 5-year overview of the GCC stock markets’ liquidity (traded value) reveals a falling trend. Saudi Arabia value traded almost halved from over $529 billion in 2014 to a little over $235 billion in 2018, While UAE shed more than 80% of its value from its peak in 2014.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[190]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Real GDP Growth Rate (in %)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The inflation-adjusted GDP growth in all economies of the Arabian Gulf region is poised to gather momentum from this year through 2021. As the infographics shows, Saudi Arabia, Oman and Kuwait are forecast to see a great leap from negative GDP growth in 2017 to a positive one from this year. Oil price stabilization is expected to ease fiscal pressure and enable governments to adopt expansionary fiscal stance that should, in turn, boost GDP growth.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[192]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[THINK TANKS IN GCC]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[These are interesting times in the Gulf as the region is undergoing seismic socio-economic transformation. As the oil-based economies move towards a post-oil future, the role of think tanks to provide the crucial research support as well as the assessment of the effectiveness of these efforts assumes significance. As shown in the chart below, the region is home to some of the leading think tanks which have been making strides in recent years and assisting decision-making. The question now is: What’s the next step in their evolution?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[194]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait Banks]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait banks ROA and ROE remain fairly strong. ]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[322]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Apple Sales by Various segments]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Strong iPhone sales propel Apple towards landmark trillion dollar market valuation.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[757]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Annual pretax income threshold to be in the top 1% of earners]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The income of top 1% of earners in a country is often used as a metric to judge its income standards. However, the quantum of income required to be a part of that elite group varies widely between countries. For instance, one needs to earn nearly twice as much in the GCC (on an average) than in the U.S. to make it to the top 1% earners.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[759]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Timeline of Saudi Arabia's inclusion In Emerging Market Indices]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Global index providers MSCI and FTSE Russell have upgraded Saudi Arabia to Emerging Market status. FTSE Russell will be implementing a five phase transition process with the 5th phase to be completed in March of 2020. MSCI is following a two phase implementation process with the second phase to be completed in August of 2019. How much capital inflow can we expect into Saudi Arabia from the index inclusion?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[761]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Distribution of Expatriate Workforce In Kuwait]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The profession wise distribution of Kuwait’s expatriate workforce reveals interesting dynamics. Non-domestic blue collar work comprising labor in mining, construction, manufacturing and transport engages the maximum number of expats at 32%, followed by human and domestic services that employ the unskilled expat population. In what can be viewed as a clear response to Kuwaitization policy, the number of expatriates working in the public sector is the lowest at 0.03 percent.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[763]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Expectation of low oil price pose challenge to budgetary Finance For Most GCC States]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Low oil price in 2019 could hamper the spending plans of GCC governments.
Fiscal break even oil price for most GCC states is much higher than expectations.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[765]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Stock Market Liquidity]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Liquidity has been one of the key issues grappling the GCC stock markets in recent years. In spite of the reforms initiated by Capital Market authorities in the GCC, the turnover ratio has fallen steeply in 2018 for all GCC countries except Bahrain when compared to 2014.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[767]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Do Technology stocks spend money on R&D]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[What do the spending patterns of FAANG stocks look like? Who spends the most for R&D and which firm spends the most to market their product?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[769]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Saudi Aramco Bond Issuance]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Debut international bond from Saudi Aramco drew unprecedented interest from yield starved investors.
Order book swelled by 10x and Aramco pulled off a remarkable feat of achieving lower borrowing costs than the Saudi Government.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[771]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Inclusion of GCC Countries to the JPM EMBI will lower the overall risk of the Index]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The inclusion of #GCC Fixed Income is a landmark moment and could signal the opening of a new chapter in the regional capital markets. The GCC region with its high reserve levels, investment grade ratings and low volatility offer significant opportunities to reduce risk. Inclusion in the benchmark J.P Morgan Emerging Market Index (JPM EMBI) could lower the overall risk of the index.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region|Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[773]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[How Competitive are GCC Economies? Doing Business Ranking]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[At the global rank of 11, the UAE has the most improved score in Ease of Doing Business ranking in the GCC in 2018. The distant second spot is occupied by Bahrain with the global rank of 62. Barring the UAE, all other GCC countries require to significantly adopt large-scale reforms and improve business conditions.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[775]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait's non-hydrocarbon sector remains resilient as economic growth is on the rise]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait’s economy has been under pressure ever since oil prices fell in 2014, as the slowdown in economic activity took its toll on the non-hydrocarbon sector as well. Supportive fiscal policy in the past few years has seen capital expenditure grow, which has, in turn, helped Kuwait’s non-oil economy to rebound. Continued capital expenditure and structural reforms are expected to provide further impetus to the non-oil sector and supplement its steady growth in the coming years.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[777]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Sovereign Bond Yields (10 Yrs)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[GCC’s government debt capital market has grown significantly in the last few years. The GCC governments have been among the biggest debt issuers globally, and investors have poured in billions of dollars in regional sovereign bonds. The chart shows comparative yields on 10-year GCC government bonds, with yields on Oman being the highest while Kuwait being the lowest. The bottomline is: With lower volatility and attractive yields, GCC sovereign bonds have emerged as more attractive asset class.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[783]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[World's Largest Cities: How the pecking order is changing]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The world’s urban population has grown rapidly in the last few decades. What’s more interesting is that future increases in the size of the world’s population are expected to be highly concentrated in just a handful of the world’s largest cities. As the diagram below shows, Asia’s largest cities together will account for around two-third of the overall projected population of world’s 10 largest cities in 2035.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[786]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Fiscal Balance ( as a % of GDP)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Stronger oil revenues, pick-up in the non-oil sector growth, and fiscal and structural reforms will help GCC economies to strike a right balance between revenues and expenditure in the near term. As the infographics below shows, most GCC countries are expected to see tangible improvements in their fiscal positions, although they are forecast to remain in negative territory in Saudi Arabia and Bahrain despite the improvement.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[788]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Current Account Balance ( as a % of GDP)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The recent recovery in oil prices and the easing of fiscal consolidation are boosting near-term growth prospects of the GCC economies. Look at the infographics below that explains how their current account balance, as a percentage of GDP, is projected to recover in 2018 and 2019. However, the hard truth is: much of this positive outlook remains subject to volatility in the future course of oil prices.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[791]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Inflation Rate (in %)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[GCC countries are projected to see the inflation level hardening in 2018 through 2021 from 2017 level. The recovery in oil prices is encouraging more pro-growth fiscal policies in the GCC, prompting governments to push fiscal spending and expansionary budgeting course. However, this fiscal push coupled with the effects of the VAT and rising fuel prices, runs the risk of fueling inflationary trends. Will rising inflation hurt the regions’ growth prospects?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[794]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Power of Passport - GCC Comparison]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Not all passports are the same when it comes to having cross-border access around the globe. The citizens of the #GCC countries are slowly, but surely, becoming more global and more powerful, if their passports are any indication. Take for instance, the holders of the UAE passport who can now travel to 167 countries (the most by any passport holder) without the need for pre-visa requirements. As the diagram below shows, rest of the GCC countries also rank within top 55 passports globally in terms of enjoying visa-free travel.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[796]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC's Top Islamic Banks by Assets]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The Islamic banking sector continues to grow in size and dominance in the GCC region. Our infographic below takes a peek at the largest Islamic banks in the region based on their assets. Top five banks capture 60% assets share.

Five of the 19 biggest banks are based in Kuwait, 4 each in the UAE and Bahrain, and 3 each in Saudi Arabia and Qatar.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[802]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[YTD 2018 Returns of GCC Equity Indices]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[In many ways the story of the GCC equity markets in 2018 has been the one of two extremes. On one end of the spectrum is Dubai benchmark that remains the biggest drag, on the other end is Qatar that blazed the trail. But then 2 key questions arise: One, have the recent sell-offs made valuations attractive in Dubai and Oman? Two, are some stock market highs in the GCC justified?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[804]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Private Sector Credit Growth (in %)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Subdued oil prices, over the last few years, have impacted private sector credit growth in the GCC region owing to a weak macroeconomic backdrop and muted non-oil economic growth. As the diagram below shows, as oil prices have been rebounding, albeit slowly, this is expected to propel private sector credit growth in 2018 in most of the Arabian Gulf countries except in Qatar. The key question is: Will the stagnant private sector lending weigh on GCC banks and impact their margins?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[808]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[3 month Deposit rate in the GCC]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The cooling eurozone economy and its easy monetary policy are reflected in the deposit rate (the rate at which banks park funds at the central bank) which is in negative territory. By contrast, higher deposit rates in the US reflect recovery of the American economy. Same is the case in the GCC region which, due to their currencies’ peg to the dollar, follow the US monetary policy. The question is: Will this global monetary policy divergence lead to global imbalances?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[811]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Global Financial Centre Index (GFCI) Rankings]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Cities around the world, as well as across the MiddleEast, are encouraging innovation and putting in place best practices in order to differentiate themselves as competition between financial centres intensifies. As shown in the diagram below, New York saw its ranking improve on the Global Financial Centres Index (GFCI) from being second in 2017 to claim the top position this year. Likewise, in the Middle East, Dubai climbed to 15th rank in 2018 on the GFCI, from 19th position in 2017.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region|Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[814]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Ease of Doing Business Parameters - Kuwait 2017 - 2019]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[A comparison of World Bank’s ‘Doing Business’ reports of last three years – 2017, 2018, 2019 -- shows Kuwait has improved, though marginally, on the overall ease of doing business parameter. Performance across sub parameters varies though.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[817]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Capital Flows (in USD Bn)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[During 2003-2007, the GCC region enjoyed positive capital flows buoyed by high growth and rising oil prices. However, the global financial-crisis in 2009 severely impacted the capital flows as foreign investors withdrew their positions. Consequently, as the chart below shows, since 2013 the region has been seeing the loss of capital. The net capital flows are expected to be negative until 2020, though the gap between resident and non-resident capital flows has been reducing. The question is: Is it capital flight or normal flows?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[819]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Fiscal Breakeven Oil Price]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The year-on-year fall in the fiscal breakeven oil price of the UAE, Saudi Arabia, Bahrain and Oman in 2018 are expected to bring relief to them. In contrast, as the diagram shows, the economies of Kuwait and Qatar are likely to continue feeling the pain, as the rise in their fiscal breakeven oil price this year, compared to 2017, is likely to keep their balance sheets under pressure.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[823]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Banking Sector - Risk Return Metrics]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Generally speaking, investing in any #asset involves the risk-return tradeoff. This means the higher the risk, the higher the potential return. As shown in the chart below, the 5-year return of different banking stock indices across the GCC has been moving in tandem with the level of risks associated. For instance, Dubai’s banking index offers the highest return, but it also carries the highest risk. Likewise, Kuwait’s banking stocks are least risky but they offer the lowest returns. The bottomline: No pain, no gain.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[825]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Foreign Direct Investment]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The softening of #crude oil prices over the last few years has taken a toll on the Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) inflows in the GCC region. This year, however, FDI inflows have so far held up relatively well and are expected to be higher than in 2017. Last year saw FDI in Saudi Arabia, Qatar and Kuwait take a sharp dip compared to 2016. Overall, the UAE continues to lead the pack in the region in terms of attracting highest FDI inflows for the last 3 years, consecutively.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[827]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Saudi 5yr bond yield spread widens against similar rated countries]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Going by the conventional metrics used by economists, rising sovereign bond yields flash warning signs for a country’s economic trajectory. Currently, the widening spread between Saudi Arabia’s 5-year bond yields and those of similar rated countries imply higher risk perception among investors about the Kingdom’s economy. The key question: is the widening yield temporary or something that is here to stay?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global|Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[829]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Spread Between Saudi Index And MSCI EM P/E TTM]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[In June 2018, the #Saudi Stock Exchange (Tadawul) had won MSCI Emerging Market (EM) status, after Tadawul fulfilled MSCI’s requirements to join EM index. However, the valuation gap between stocks in Saudi Arabia and EM has been expanding for around a year, and currently, Saudi Arabian stocks are trading at a premium compared to the MSCI EM Index. What’s pushing Saudi stocks’ valuations, and is it a good time for investors?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global|Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[831]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Expat Proportion(%) of total population in GCC]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[These GCC countries have the highest (and lowest) expat-to-local population mix.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[833]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Top 5 Nationalities in Kuwait Labour Market]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Revealed: The top 5 nationalities in Kuwait workforce.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[835]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Petrol Prices in Selected Emerging Economies]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The real cost of filling up: Petrol prices in Emerging Markets &amp; GCC.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region|Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[837]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Are GCC Citizens Richer Now?]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Guess, which GCC country has the highest, and lowest GDP per capita growth!]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[839]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait Jobs 2017 - Arabic]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait unemployment : Women dominate]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[841]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait Jobs 2017]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait unemployment : Women dominate]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[843]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Turmoil in Turkey]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Turkey Economic pains, how will it play out.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[845]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Bahrain]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Bahrain’s government debt expected to be 85% of GDP in 2018; nearly doubles since 2014.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Bahrain]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[847]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Global Islamic Bond issuance]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Global Islamic Bond issuance was dull, dropped by 15.3% in H1 2018 compared to same period last year.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[849]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Bahrain]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Bahrain foreign exchange reserves shrink by over 75% since its peak in 2014 of USD 5,758Mn.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Bahrain]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[853]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Dubai Stocks - Sectoral Performance (YTD 2018)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Consumer &amp; realestate stocks weigh down on Dubai’s market performance.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[855]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait Banks - Moody's Rating Distribution]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Majority of Kuwait banks hold upper medium #investment grade rating by Moody’s.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[862]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[US Trade Deficit with Trade Partners]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[US picks on its major trade allies sparking a potential TradeWar.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[864]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Bahrain 5-Yr CDS Spreads 2018]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Announcement of financial relief from neighbors provides temporary respite for Bahrain.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Bahrain]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[866]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia - Oil Revenue As A Part of Total Revenue]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[SaudiArabia stepping up effort to reduce its reliance on Oil revenues.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[868]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Banking Stock Market Performance]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Dubai Banking Index outperform other #GCC banking indices between May 2012 to June 2018.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[870]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait Listed Banks Stock Market Performance]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait Finance House outperforms other banks in Kuwait during past 5 years till June 2018. ]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[872]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait Banks Stock Market Performance]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Comparative performance of Kuwait Banks.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[874]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[New Visa Regime Can the new visa regime maintain GCC economy's competitive edge?]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Changing visa rules in the #GCC – Will this help the region retain its competitiveness?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[876]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Bond Markets Signal Tensions]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Widening CDS spread indicates brewing financial troubles for Bahrain.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[879]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[MENA Top 100 Companies]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Mena Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[882]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait Banking]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Impact of Fintech, in Kuwait Banking industry.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[884]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[IPhone Price Index]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[One iPhone, many nations, different prices.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[886]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Royal's Contribution to UK Economy]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The Business of Royal Monarchy.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[888]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait - No of Employees and Their wages]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait public sector employee base has grown about 5% every year, while wage bill has risen by about 9%.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[890]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Renewable Energy]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Renewable energy paves the roadmap for the future of energy across MiddleEast.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[892]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Jabel Ali Free Zone (JAFZA)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[JAFZA reaffirmed as key trading hub Trade valued at $83bn (2017); Middle East tops.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[894]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Liquidity in UAE Banks Abundant As of Now]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Impact of Fintech, in UAE Banking industry]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[896]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Dubai's 3D Printing Strategy]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Dubai’s 3D printing infrastructure road-map can prove to be a template to overcome GCC construction sector woes.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[898]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Burgeoning GCC Debt Profile]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[GCC is actively looking at debt as a source of financing – the trend that was earlier missing.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[900]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Domestic and International Passengers Carried by Airlines in Major Markets]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The US, Europe, and China carry far more air passengers than the GCC and India.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[902]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Companies in China]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[GCC Companies footprints in China.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region|Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[904]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Companies In India]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[GCC Companies footprints in India.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region|Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[906]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[KSA Banking Sector 2018]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The fintech revolution is likely to have a significant impact particularly on the retail #banking business in Saudi Arabia . ]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[908]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[The GCC Ritz-Carlton Index - Price per night]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[GCC hotel room rates inequality - One hotel brand, different locations, different rates]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[910]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Banking Sector 2018]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Fintech can disrupt more than 15% business of GCC Banks in next 5 years.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[912]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Conglomerates - Global Footprints]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[GCC companies have been spreading globally. Let's find out who are those and how deep they penetrate.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region|Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[914]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Speed Test Global Index]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Which country in the GCC has the top internet Broadband Speed?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region|Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[916]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[SME Startups]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Featuring Successful SME Startups in GCC]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[918]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[How Brexit Stacks up against the Global Financial Crisis of 2008?]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[920]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Saudi Economic Posts Reshuffle]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[May 2016]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[922]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Crisis: Here to Stay]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The Known "Unknowns"!]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2045]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Key Players in GCC Sharing Economy]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Sharing economy entails collaborative consumption that promotes concepts like community ownership, localized production, growth of small-scale enterprise, improved economic and environmental consciousness. Who are the key players in GCC sharing economy?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2139]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Ridesharing Platforms Operating in GCC]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The GCC region witnessed its biggest tech deal wherein Uber acquired Careem, the most prominent ride sharing player in the region in a deal worth $3.1 billion. What does this reveal about the present and future of ride sharing market in GCC?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2208]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Online Food Delivery Sites and Apps with Strong Presence across GCC]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[How are marketing innovations, and lifestyle changes of GCC consumers affecting the business in restaurants and online food ordering and delivery services?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2210]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[M&A Activities in GCC Restaurant tech space]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Food delivery services contributed a gross revenue of USD 284.9 million to the GCC economy in 2018. The GCC food delivery sector is lively with a strong growth and multiple M&A deals. Find out about the prominent deals in GCC Restaurant tech - Marmore Research Report.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2212]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Remittance Charges to India]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Qatar, the fifth largest remitter to India, has the highest remittance cost to India among GCC countries.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2224]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Restaurant tech startups in key segments]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[With a 77% smart phone penetration in the GCC, the region is witnessing the emergence of a new section of digital customers which has its repercussions across industries. Who are the key food tech startups in the GCC region?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2260]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Remittance charges to Pakistan]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia, which accounts for the highest remittance inflows into Pakistan, also has the highest remittance cost to Pakistan among GCC countries. ]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2273]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Key Trends in Restaurant Tech]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Cooked? Baked? 3D printed? How do you prefer your food? Read about how restaurants across the GCC use enabling technologies to cater to customers. ]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2290]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Oman and Bahrain's spreads widen after downgrade in credit ratings]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Here is where the CDS spreads of GCC countries stand in comparison with global peers.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region|Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2311]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Remittance charges to Bangladesh]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The UAE, whose remittance outflow to Bangladesh stood at USD 2.4 billion in 2017, has the lowest remittance cost to Bangladesh among GCC countries.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2317]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Remittance charges to Philippines]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know? Saudi Arabia has the highest remittance cost to Philippines among GCC countries.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2321]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Expat proportion (%) of total population in GCC states]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Which countries has the highest expat proportion in GCC.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2367]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[iPhone 11 Pro Max - Price Index (256 GB)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Prices of iPhone across globe, where to buy the next iPhone?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2394]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Power of Passport - GCC Comparison]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Passport power for GCC nations status upgraded...]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2516]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Ease of Doing Business Parameters – Kuwait 2018 – 2020]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait jumps 14 points up at ease of doing business released by World bank, How did it fare across parameters?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2584]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Salaries in the Middle East: How they compare across functions?]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[How salaries differ across designations? What can one expect to draw in the Middle East?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Mena Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2596]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait Banks - Stock Market Performance (2019)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[How have Kuwaiti banks fared in 2019?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2704]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[What value would Aramco trade at?]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Saudi Aramco would start trading from 11th December onwards, post listing what do you think the stock would trade at?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[2729]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Equity Indices 2019 YTD Performance]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait stock market outperforms regional peers with YTD gains of 17% (as of 28th Nov) amid investor euphoria on MSCI’s announcement on reclassification of the Kuwait to emerging market status.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region|Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3029]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Science and Engineering journal articles published per million population, 2018]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Most GCC states lag behind world average in Science & Engineering research]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3124]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait - High Growth Sectors (2010 - 2018)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Basic metals and Chemicals – highest growing sector in Kuwait.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3243]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwaiti Economy - Average Growth Sectors (2010 - 2018)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Social work, defense and cultural services sectors witnessed above average growth during 2010-18]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3409]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Brokerages call on Saudi Aramco]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[How much did brokerages value Saudi Aramco post its listing?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3418]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Sectors with Negative Growth in Kuwait (2010 - 18)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Wood and Food & Beverages de-grew the most during 2010-2018.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3457]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[IPOs in GCC Region, 2013 - 2019]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Managing and exiting investments made by PE and VC is a key hurdle stifling the growth of the industry. IPOs remain a less frequent exit route for GCC SMEs.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3637]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC PE Firms - Investments transactions by country, 2008-2019]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[UAE firms have been involved in more PE transactions between 2008 and 2019 than the rest of the GCC combined.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3688]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Global Powertrain Market Share 2015- 2030]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Globally there is a growing shift towards Electric Vehicles (EV). What are the factors driving EV demand and their expected demand in GCC countries.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region|Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3704]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Net Passenger Vehicles Imports by Value]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[In 2014 Saudi Arabia accounted for the largest share of passenger vehicle market by value in the GCC. How has this changed in 2018? What could be the share over the next 5 years?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[3947]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Exposure of Norway's Sovereign Wealth Fund (SWF) to GCC Equities]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[UAE and Kuwait dominate Norway’s SWF equity investments in GCC. For 2018-19, value of the investments increased the most in Kuwait]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4246]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Equities face unprecedented fall amid coronavirus]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Markets have usually recovered within a year from outbreaks.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4253]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Previous outbreaks have had lesser impact on Kuwait equities]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Has the fall in Kuwait equities from coronavirus (COVID-19) been steeper than previous outbreaks?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4452]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC 5year Credit Default Swap (CDS) Spreads]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[As fears of a global recession have grown GCC sovereign CDS spreads, a key measure of credit risk, have jumped markedly - tripling or quadrupling in some cases.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4454]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[10-year U.S Treasury Yield (%)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Yields stay low as investors flock to safe haven assets.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4470]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Gold, Oil & Currency - 28th April]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Oil price tumbles amid continued supply, drop in demand and storage woes]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4533]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[In how many days does COVID-19 Confirmed cases doubles in GCC Countries?]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Check our latest chart on COVID-19: Number of days in which confirmed COVID cases are doubling in GCC.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4537]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Doubling time and Fatality rate]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[COVID-19: Which GCC Countries are faring better with lower fatality rates and high number of days required to double?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4539]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Most of the GCC REITs are trading at 52 week lows]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[REITs have been hit hard on expectations of lower occupancy and falling rents amid lockdown.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4543]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Impact on different Banking services due to COVID-19]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[How Covid-19 is affecting banking services?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4579]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Monetary policy action by GCC Central Banks in response to COVID-19]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[With GCC Central Banks in action Interest Rates cut and Financial Stimulus were announced. Find out the quantum of support provided so far.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4620]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Revision to GCC’s 2020 Fiscal Forecasts due to change in oil prices and COVID-19]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[COVID19 and volatility in oil prices make the outlook for GCC uncertain. How have it impacted the IMF's 2020 forecasts for the region? ]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4649]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Quarterly IPO activity, 2013-2019]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Managing and exiting investments made by Private Equity and Venture Capital is a key hurdle stifling the growth of the industry. IPOs remain a less frequent exit route for GCC SMEs.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4709]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Share prices of GCC REITs compared with 52 week highs and lows]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[COVID19 Impact: Most of the REITs in GCC are trading near their 52-week lows, what are the performance expectations in the short term?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4782]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Global COVID-19 confirmed cases are accelerating]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[While April glimpsed just 2 days of more than 100,000 daily new cases globally, May spotted it for 8 days, and June all along; Is 100,000 daily cases a new normal? ]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4839]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC COVID-19 daily new cases and deaths trend]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Will UAE soon be hailed triumphant in winning the fight against COVID-19; the country’s daily cases and deaths dives down in contrast to elsewhere in GCC.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4997]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Return Expectations for the next 10 years for Global markets]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[COVID-19 has revised long term equity return expectations for global markets. What can we expect for Saudi equities?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[4998]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Results of Socila Media Poll - Return expectation for Saudi Arabia 2020-2024]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[We conducted a poll in Saudi Equity returns, here are the results!
How important is it to develop equity market returns platform for Saudi Arabia, read our article]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5053]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Countries comparison of Testing and number of cases per million]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[On a per million population basis UAE fairs the best both in terms of tests conducted and least number of confirmed cases reported. How does other GCC Countries fare on these parameters?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5147]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Investor risk appetite has improved in the GCC region]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Market volatility & sovereign spreads have eased as risk appetite has returned in the GCC region.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5163]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Covid unable to infect Tesla]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Tesla on top gear as its equity shares witness strong rally despite coronavirus disruption]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5178]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Performance of Global Sector Indices]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Investors pile on technology sector as COVID-19 pandemic accelerates shift to a more digital world]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5189]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Performance of Commodities]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[In the current Covid chaos, Gold is a clear winner]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5195]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Performance of U.S Tech Giants]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[U.S tech giants trounce economic catastrophe to emerge as clear winners.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5253]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Performance of Travel & Hospitality Stocks]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Coronavirus has taken its toll on travel industry. Airlines and hotels struggle to survive]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5306]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Performance of Global Market Indices]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[China and U.S stocks recover from COVID-19 effects faster than others. UK, France and Italy lags.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5445]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Performance of U.S 10-year Treasury Bond]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[US treasury yield moves lower as US Fed holds interest rates steady]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5491]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC COVID-19 mobility trends]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[While GCC mobility recovered from the May's drop, it has remained relatively flat in June and July indicating a slow or plateaued recovery]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5502]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Performance of GCC Sovereign CDS Spreads]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[GCC Sovereign CDS spreads ease as economic conditions improve]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[5627]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Evolution of Cost of Capital in the GCC]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[In the GCC region - Cost of capital, a key metric to value investments, has evolved over the years. What has been the impact of COVID-19?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6154]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia's export of key items to USA is just a fraction of China's exports to USA, can this change?]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Could frictions between U.S. & China be a window of opportunity for KSA.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6183]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE's export of key items to USA is just a fraction of China's exports to USA, can this change?]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Could frictions between U.S. & China be a window of opportunity for UAE.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6187]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[In Comparison to China, Kuwait barely exports to the USA. Can this change?]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Can trade war between U.S. & China be an opportunity for Kuwait to increase its exports to the USA?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6204]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Qatar's export of key items to USA is just a fraction of China's exports to USA, can this change?]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Could frictions between U.S. & China be a window of opportunity for Qatar.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Qatar]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6398]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[U.S Treasury Yield and GDP Deflator]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Could the secular decline in yields survive COVID-19 induced liquidity glut? ]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6445]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia Treasury Yield & GDP Deflator]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Could higher inflation threaten the splendid rally in KSA Sovereign bonds?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6448]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Qatar Treasury Yield & GDP Deflator]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Investors lap up Qatar sovereign bonds as yields plummet. How low could the yields go?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Qatar]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6449]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Market Performance]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Market Performance]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6922]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait - Daily New Covid Cases]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know? 
Kuwait is facing a more acute second wave of COVID19]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6924]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait population by Age, 2019]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Kuwait population pyramid-untypical bulge]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6926]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia Economic Indicators]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Services dominate in Saudi GDP as much as Oil]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6929]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE – Daily New Covid Cases]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know: UAE faces an acute second wave of the virus, which peaked in February and have since subsided.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6932]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[KSA Fiscal Position, Debt & Reserves]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[The fiscal triangle of Saudi Arabia: Higher deficit, higher debt, and lower reserves.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6940]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[India Covid-19 Daily New Cases]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know: India faces an acute second wave of the virus, which is much steeper and yet to peak.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6943]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE Economic Activity, GDP]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[UAE enjoys a diversified services sector.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6951]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Banking Indicators - UAE]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Banking assets in UAE are twice as much as its GDP]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6953]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Qatar Covid-19 Daily New Cases]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know: Post steep first wave of the virus, the second wave is yet building up in Qatar.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Qatar]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6957]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Bahrain Covid-19 Daily New Cases]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know: In Bahrain, current new COVID-19 cases as a percentage of earlier peak is at 1.21x.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Bahrain]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6959]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE Trade Statistics]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[UAE imports the most from China and India, while India is its top export destination as well.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6962]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[USA Covid-19 Daily New Cases]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know: While most of the nations are into second wave of COVID-19, USA is about to have a 4th wave. Each subsequent wave had a new higher peak as the second wave peak was 1.11 times higher than the first wave peak, and third wave peak was 2.96 times higher than the second wave.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6965]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Ease of Doing Business Rankings - UAE]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Starting a business, getting credit, and protecting minority interest witnessed major improvements, resulting in significant improvement in UAE's Ease of Doing Business Rankings.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6970]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Labour Market]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia, Bahrain, and Oman has better representation of Nationals working in the private sector, whereas other GCC countries lag.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6972]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[UK Covid-19 Daily New Cases]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know: UK just got over its second wave which had a peak higher by 12.4 times compared to it's first wave. Would UK see another wave in 2021?]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6978]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Qatar Global Competitiveness Ranking]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Qatar showed substantial improvement in ICT adoption, but faltered on other parameters which led to drop in its global competitiveness ranking.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Qatar]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6980]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Total Cases per million]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know: On COVID-19 Cases per Million basis - Bahrain is the worst affected country in the GCC, while Saudi Arabia has managed really well to contain the spread.
]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6983]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC - New Covid-19 Tests Performed per Thousand People]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know: UAE leads in terms of testing more people for COVID-19, followed by Bahrain. Other GCC countries are yet to catch up. ]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6993]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC's Fiscal Breakeven Oil Price]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Oil prices are back to pre-covid levels and are cushioning the borrowing requirements of the region. ]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6996]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Germany new COVID-19 cases]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know: As Germany weathers the third wave of COVID-19 it has imposed strict lockdown measures to contain the spread. ]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[6999]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC Current Account Balance (% GDP)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[ Except UAE, all other GCC nations are expected to post a negative current account balance. ]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[7005]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Italy new COVID-19 cases]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know: In Italy (currently in third wave), any region with more than 250 COVID cases per 100,000 is placed under "red" category meaning bars, restaurants and schools must close. ]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[7016]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[France new COVID-19 cases]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know: France might have crossed the peak of the third wave of the Covid-19 pandemic, as schools would open and restrictions confining people to a 10-kilometre (six-mile) radius of their homes would be dropped from May 3]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[7023]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Ease of Doing Business]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Except UAE, Ease of doing Business rankings improved for all other GCC countries in 2020]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[7118]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Global Competitiveness]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[In 2020, all GCC nations witnessed improvement in Global Competitiveness rankings, except Oman.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[7120]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[GCC New COVID-19 cases per million]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know: Only Qatar and UAE managed to bring down their new COVID-19 reported cases on a per million people bases, while there has been slight deterioration for other GCC nations in the month of April.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[7126]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[% of GCC Population infected with COVID-19]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know: Despite being the most populous country in the GCC region, only 1.2% of the total population was infected with COVID-19 virus in Saudi Arabia, while in Bahrain about 10.4% of the population was infected with the virus.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[7133]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[% of Population Vaccinated]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Did you know: USA is one of the most active nations in terms of vaccination drive as it is close to vaccinate about one-third of its population against COVID-19 virus.
]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[7728]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Weight of Countries in MSCI EM Index]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[GCC countries have low weightage in MSCI EM Index compared to leading emerging markets]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[7750]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[MSCI EM Index by Sector]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Energy sector has low weightage in MSCI EM Index impacting GCC stocks]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[7818]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Weightage in MSCI EM in %]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Top GCC Companies in the MSCI EM Index]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Global]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[8153]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Cost of Capital for GCC Countries - H1 2021]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Cost of capital under the three methods with average]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[8448]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia Healthcare Spending]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia has been consistently increasing healthcare spending in recent years, though it lags behind developed economies on a per-capita basis.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[8474]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Kuwait A Popular Luxury Retail Destination]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Affluent population and increasing consumer spending augur well for Kuwait as a leading luxury retail destination]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Kuwait]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[8477]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Covid-19 Impacted UAE's F&B Sales]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[COVID-19 impacted UAE’s F&B sales and the sector is expected to recover in the coming five years.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[8480]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Saudi Aramco Largest and Most Profitable Oil Company]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Saudi Aramco is not only the largest but also the most profitable oil company in the World
]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[8575]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Fiscal breakeven oil price for MENA Oil exporters (USD/bbl)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Oil exporters could accrue gains as OPEC+ resists calls to accelerate production]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[GCC Region]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[8875]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Residential Market Gross Rental Yield (%)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[Rental yields in UAE remain relatively high (nearly 6%). High yields incentivize investors who need steady stream of income.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates]]></categories>
	</node>
	<node>
		<id><![CDATA[8889]]></id>
		<title><![CDATA[Residential Market Price-to-Income Ratio (Years)]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[UAE residential real estate scores high on affordability quotient as it shifted focus from luxury segment towards affordable projects.]]></content>
		<categories><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates]]></categories>
	</node>
</data>
